<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>The Swami 3</title><link>http://swami3.com/</link><description>Recent content on The Swami 3</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 19:42:04 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://swami3.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Concerts</title><link>http://swami3.com/concerts/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 19:42:04 +0800</pubDate><guid>http://swami3.com/concerts/</guid><description> .concerthead { font-size: 21px; } 2022 Singapore British Club Concert 2021 Rockaway Avenue Concert 2018 June Recital 2017 June Recital</description></item><item><title>Contact Us</title><link>http://swami3.com/contact/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 19:42:04 +0800</pubDate><guid>http://swami3.com/contact/</guid><description>body { background-color: #c90404; } #form { border: 5px solid gold; margin: 0px 10vw 0px 10vw; padding: 20px 0px 20px 0px; text-align: center; } .form-row { margin: 10px 0px 10px 0px; } .input-field { display: inline-block; text-align: left; margin: 0px 5% 0px 5%; } .form-input { border: none; outline: none; border-radius: 5px; padding: 7px; background-color: lightgray; font-size: 17px; font-family: 'Roboto', sans-serif; width: 100%; } .form-input:hover { background-color: darkgray; cursor: pointer; } Subject:</description></item><item><title>Noah</title><link>http://swami3.com/noah/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 19:42:04 +0800</pubDate><guid>http://swami3.com/noah/</guid><description>body { text-align: center; background-color: gold; } #head { font-size: 35px; } #aboutnoah { text-align: left; } #sec1 { background: darkred; } Noah, Shaan's twin, is the guitarist in the Swami 3. He started playing the classical guitar when he was 5, and practiced for 30 minutes a day. Before long he had learned a variety of songs; some electric/rock, and some classical. When he was 7, he learned to play with his brothers as a band.</description></item><item><title>Rohan</title><link>http://swami3.com/rohan/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 19:42:04 +0800</pubDate><guid>http://swami3.com/rohan/</guid><description>body { text-align: center; background-color: #c90404; } #aboutrohan { text-align: left; } #sec1, #sec3, #sec5 { background-color: gold; } Ever since Rohan reluctantly started learning piano at age 5, it has become his greatest passion. He started out following the Faber lesson books - but that only lasted him a few years. Once he finished all five levels of the books and was ready to move on, his teacher started giving him all sorts of new pieces to learn, including classical pieces, recent music, band pieces to play with his brothers (of course), and jazz sheets where he has opportunities to improvise.</description></item><item><title>Shaan</title><link>http://swami3.com/shaan/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 19:42:04 +0800</pubDate><guid>http://swami3.com/shaan/</guid><description>body { background-color: blue; color: white; } #head { font-size: 35px; } #aboutshaan { text-align: left; } .shaanlink { color: white; } .shaanlink:hover { color: orange; } #sec1, #sec3 { background-color: gold; } My name is Shaan. I am 12 years old and play the drums and sing. I started learning drums and vocals when I was 5, when our parents thought we should learn music and chose instruments for us that fit our personalities.</description></item><item><title>Songs</title><link>http://swami3.com/songs/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 19:42:04 +0800</pubDate><guid>http://swami3.com/songs/</guid><description>body { background-color: darkred; } #sec1, #sec3, #sec5, #sec7, #sec9, #sec11 { background-color: gold; } Coming soon: Don't Fear the Reaper by Blue Öyster Cult, Miserlou by Dick Dale, Don't Stop Believing by Journey Livin' on a Prayer by Bon Jovi Mr. Blue Sky by Electric Light Orchestra Run Rudolph Run by Chuck Berry Starman by Davie Bowie Bennie and the Jets by Elton John I Bet That You Look Good on the Dancefloor by Arctic Monkeys Havana by Camila Cabello Eye of the Tiger by Survivor Don't Stop Me Now by Queen Merry Xmas Everybody by Slade Bohemian Rhapsody by Queen Soul Killing by The Ting Tings I Will Survive by Gloria Gaynor American Pie by Don McLean That Thing You Do by The Wonders Come Together by The Beatles 12 Bar Blues Magic by Coldplay Imagine by John Lennon Lady Madonna by the Beatles Winter Wonderland by Felix Bernard Hall of Fame by The Script (feat.</description></item><item><title>Teacher Phil Surtees</title><link>http://swami3.com/phil/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 19:42:04 +0800</pubDate><guid>http://swami3.com/phil/</guid><description>#head { font-size: 35px; } .phillink { text-decoration: none; } .phillink:hover { text-decoration: underline; } #aboutphil { text-align: left; } Phil got his start in youth as first clarinet at the City of Birmingham Wind Orchestra, and later joined the Midland Youth Jazz Orchestra. Following his degree in Music and Performing Arts he toured the UK and Europe with pop-ska band 'The Bad Robots' and indie-electro band 'Dead on Tv'.</description></item><item><title>The Band's Story</title><link>http://swami3.com/origin/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 19:42:04 +0800</pubDate><guid>http://swami3.com/origin/</guid><description>When Rohan was five, the family walked past Russo Music in San Francisco. That's when Rohan's mom decided to put him in piano classes; he was not happy about that. But over the years, Rohan grew to love music. Then Noah started learning guitar, and Shaan started learning drums. The Swaminathans had a small electric keyboard in their house, Shaan got a shiny blue drum set for Christmas, and Noah had already been moving through a lot of guitars.</description></item></channel></rss>